RAVI PRAKASH PARMAR

LINKEDIN | GITHUB | WEBSITE

+91 8989404875 • raviprakashparmar3@gmail.com

Objective - Driven by deadlines and a strong work ethic, I am a resourceful and passionate with excellent organisational skills. With over two years of experience at a college-level organisation, I have demonstrated success in writing, project management, team leadership, and schedule coordination. I am eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail, and a commitment to excellent organisational practices. Always seeking new opportunities to learn and expand my knowledge, I am enthusiastic about exploring emerging technologies for the betterment of society.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD

Master of Computer Application

Ujjain, MP

November 2021 -July 2023

Hyderabad, TA

MADHAV SCIENCE COLLEGE, VIKRAM UNIVERSITY

Bachelors of Science

July 2017 -Jun 2020

SKILLS

HTML **JavaScript** Iava MvSOL **Prompt Engineering**

Latex Content writer PowerPoint Team Leadership Team Management Management

Collaboration Proofreading Copy Editing Subtitling

INTERNSHIP

Blue stock Fintech, Software Development Engineer (SDE) Intern

September 2024 - October 2024

Software Development - Html, Css, Javascript.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Balsara, Marketing and Management

January 2019 - February 2020

• worked with a company to sell carry bags at shops, malls.

RS Enterprises, My Startup-Self-employed

Jun 2018 - February 2020

• Gained deep knowledge of marketing, customer acquisition. Sales, Entrepreneurship.

Freelance, Content Writer

January 2021 - Present

- We write a content of great experience for audience.
- Developed and Analysed high quality content exclusively in Hindi and English.

PROJECTS AND CONTENT DOCUMENTATION

Generic Web Application Development including Mobile App Development for White labelling

Develop a generic web application and mobile app that can be easily White labelled for use by a variety of businesses and organizations.

Event Management System

Event Management System wherein admin and user can lookup for events city and category wise and the user can book tickets (one or more at a time).

Simple Voting System

This project will first create a menu in which you will be told which party is on which number. The second task of this project is to calculate the votes cast by you, for whom you have voted. The third task of this project is to show the result of voting i.e. election.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- NSS, NCC, Writings, Sports.
- Coding Certification: 1. Centre for Development of Advanced Computing (CDAC), Pune.
 - 2. I have participated Basic Web Development Quiz organised by the Btech Wallah.

Writing Analysis Researching Chess Volunteering Reading Running Yoga